<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on SignalVsNoise</title>
    <link>https://signalvsnoise.to/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on SignalVsNoise</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.154.5</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://signalvsnoise.to/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What Is Closing Line Value (CLV)?</title>
      <link>https://signalvsnoise.to/posts/2026-01-22-what-is-closing-line-value-clv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://signalvsnoise.to/posts/2026-01-22-what-is-closing-line-value-clv/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;what-is-closing-line-value-clv&#34;&gt;What Is Closing Line Value (CLV)?&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the world of sports betting and prediction markets, the concept of Closing Line Value (CLV) is a crucial indicator of whether you are making sharp, informed wagers or falling prey to inefficiencies. But what exactly is CLV, why does it matter, and how can understanding it improve your long-term approach to betting? This article offers a clear, analytical introduction to CLV, breaking down its mechanics, illustrating it with examples, and explaining how professionals use it to assess betting skill.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Why Sportsbooks Limit Bettors</title>
      <link>https://signalvsnoise.to/posts/2026-01-22-why-sportsbooks-limit-bettors/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://signalvsnoise.to/posts/2026-01-22-why-sportsbooks-limit-bettors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;why-sportsbooks-limit-bettors&#34;&gt;Why Sportsbooks Limit Bettors&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sports betting has grown rapidly in recent years, drawing millions of people to place wagers on everything from basketball and football to niche sports and esports. But anyone who has tried to place large bets or consistently win over time may have encountered an unexpected obstacle: sportsbooks limiting how much they can bet, or even restricting their accounts altogether. Understanding why sportsbooks place these limits is key to grasping how the industry works and what bettors can realistically expect.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
